yandalo.com 2013-03-02

# Privacy Policy - Yandalo

## Cookies

###  A cookie is a small data file containing certain information and is written to your hard drive when you visit the website. A cookie cannot be read by a website other than the one that sets the cookie. Most cookies Last only through a single session or visit. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. We also use outside agencies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies that are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

## Third Parties

###  Yandalo.com works with third parties that serve ads to this site.In these instances, we have no control over the information collected by the third-party, and may not be held responsible for the actions of the third-party measurement service where collected information is concerned. If you have questions regarding different third-party measurement services and their respective methods of information collection, please [contact us](http://www.yandalo.com/contact.php). 

We use a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our site. This company may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to our and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your computer. 

## Google

###  Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

## Contact info

###  If you wish to learn more about our efforts to protect your privacy, please feel free to [send questions and/or comments](http://www.yandalo.com/contact.php). 

## Axill's privacy policy

###  Axill, as part of providing online services, may ask you to provide us with certain personal information, for example, your name, date of birth, e-mail address etc. 

Axill takes all reasonable steps to protect the privacy of our customers and ensures that the personal information we collect is not ordinarily disclosed to third parties without the customer's consent. Axill has numerous security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of our customer's information. All customer information is password protected and only accessible by authorized members of the Axill staff. 

However, there may be times when Axill may be required to disclose personal information of a customer without his/her express consent when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against the customer. 

While Axill, our associates and affiliates make every effort to protect your personal information and your privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online, that information can be collected and used by people that neither we nor you will know. 

By using this website or our affiliated websites, you signify your assent to our terms and conditions. If you do not agree to be bound by our terms, we politely ask that you do not use this.
